## Pitchayakit Pahamak Software Engineer

Last update: April 12, 2024

The online version is available at

https://pitchayakit.github.io/cv

Residence	Bangkok, Thailand
Phone	+66831225471
GitHub	<b>o</b> pitchayakit
Email	☑ pitchayakit.p@gmail.com

NodeJs	+++++	ExpressJs	+++++	Laravel	+++++	PHP	+++++	CSS	+++++	SQL	++++
Livewire	++++	AlpineJs	++++	jQuery	++++	Tailwind	++++	Bootstrap	++++	WordPress	++++
Restful	++++	GIT	++++	VueJs	+++	Linux	+++	Nginx	+++	Python	++

With over 7 years of experience in the software development industry, I have honed my skills in a diverse range of companies, including startups and digital agencies. My expertise spans all aspects of the software development lifecycle and project management. I have a particular passion for Internet of Things (IoT) and Machine Learning technologies, and am always seeking ways to leverage these to enhance everyday life.

## **Professional Experience**

#### Rocket 8

May 2023 - Present

- Collaborating with product development and design team
- Creating a Document (SSOT) for a development team
- Design User Journey, User Flow, Code pattern, Review code
- Research state of the art
- Design database schema
- Data migration from legacy system to new system
- Writing clean, testable, high-quality code
- Upgrade and maintain web applications and database for maximum performance

NodeJs ExpressJS Sequelize

#### Lexicon

Aug 2020 - Apr 2023

- Maintained web servers and managed CI/CD processes
- Developed clean, testable, and high-quality code
- Managed the Line CRM system
- Managed a CMS using Laravel, Nova, and WordPress
- Implemented and managed Elasticsearch
- Handled data migration tasks
- Mentored junior developers in web development and provided technical support



#### Freelancer

2018 - 2020

- Managed company, e-commerce, and library websites
- Upgraded and maintained web applications for optimal performance
- Collaborated closely with stakeholders to understand their unique requirements and goals

WordPress Laravel

#### **Empag**

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

- Coached interns in web development and provided technical support
- Managed web content management systems and collaborated with video and content teams to gather requirements and implement solutions
- Collaborated with designers to ensure the quality and accuracy of designs
- Developed a tool for web scraping and exporting data to Excel files

WordPress NodeJs

#### Onestockhome

Mar 2017 - Sep 2017

- Migrated content management system to Ruby on Rails platform
- Developed front-end of website using jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML, and CSS in Ruby on Rails platform
- Supported the use of content management system and improved user interface

Ruby on Rail React

#### Rippleworkz

2016 - 2017

- Integrated HTML with WordPress and Prestashop
- Managed web content management systems and multitasked effectively
- Collaborated with project manager to develop websites beyond own project scope

WordPress jQuery

# SeSaMe (Sensor-enhanced Social Media) Center, National University of Singapore

Jul 2015 - Dec 2015

- SENSE video analytics web application replaced video output for detection, tracking and counting by HTML Canvas
- Take over and developed SeSaMe website using Joomla CMS

Play Framework | HTML Canvas | Joomla | OpenCV | MongoDB

#### **Education**

Master of Network Learning Technology, College of Electrical Engineering & Computer Science, National Central University, Taiwan [2018 - 2020]

Bachelor of Computer Engineering, College of Engineering, Kasetsart University, Thailand [2013 - 2016]

### **Additional Experience**

A Study of using IoT and Zenbo robot to facilitate students' interaction in flipped classroom and the analysis of their perception.

[IoT] Zenbo | Machine learning

Smart home with door and light control system.

IoT PHP JQuery